Why?
What the hell is this?
Don't we really have any way
To punish these scoundrels?
We make a little girl
She defends her dignity with her life.
Did you see that?
I already saved you.
Is this the result you want?
Calm down.
I told you to calm down.
my lord.
Lee Lee is dead.
my dad.
Jin Wen.
Do you know?
You saved that girl.
But I saw it with my own eyes
You die in front of me.
Si Yao.
Don't do this.
This is not your fault.
Because of my disability
That girl died.
Si Yao.
Be encouraged.
I will always be by your side.
I will never allow their deaths to be mysterious.
Si Yao.
Blank police card.
Did you put it here?
There is someone.
You said the previous camera film
It was also found in the same place.
This time a blank police card.
There is someone to help us.
There is a spy among the police.
Then it must be Li Chengrui.
Maybe he's not alone.
Everyone is a suspect.
In your opinion,
Who is the person providing us with evidence?
in the end,
Why does it help us?
Detective Chu.
The bosses sent someone to ask
About Pete's death
They asked you to provide an explanation
A house worth dying for
Even if he died ten thousand times, it wouldn't be enough to quell the hatred
How should I write a case report?
Just write
That Pete raped Chinese women several times
The victim was unable to resist
So she died with him
Write it like this.
Yes.
Detective Jiang.
I heard from the neighbors
You are a just judge in this age,
It will help us poor people achieve justice.
Detective Jiang.
Get up quickly.
What happened?
I beg you,
Help me find my daughter.
Detective Jiang.
What happened to your daughter?
My daughter has been missing for three days.
I informed the police,
But the police of that area asked me to just wait.
But three days have already passed,
I couldn't wait any longer.
I beg you,
Can you investigate the matter for me?
Keep talking.
My daughter's name is Ling Ling,
She is sixteen years old.
She always sold cigarettes at the entrance of Bai Xiang Lu's dance hall.
Three days ago,
I went out to sell cigarettes as usual.
And she never came back.
Detective Jiang.
correct
This is amazing...
I have a picture of my daughter.
Don't worry,
We will open a case and start the investigation immediately.
Finally I'm back.
I've waited for you for a long time.
When I received your call,
I went to Tsui Bai Lu restaurant immediately
To bring you your favorite dish, golden meat
It's still hot
What happened?
Why do you look unhappy?
Li Chengrui from Fenghuang Police Station
It definitely has something to do with Pete's case
And Li Li's drug trafficking case
It has a relationship
Isn't this case already closed?
And this one of mine has also died
Who on earth is this Li Chengrui?
He seems cowardly and indecisive at times.
Other times it is decisive.
I saw it with my own eyes.
He kills Bai Xianming with one shot.
His throw was steady, accurate and deadly.
It's not useless
As it seems.
If we talk about this Li Cheng Rui,
Many years ago,
I didn't hear him
Below Jiang Si Yao's reputation.
I remember
That there was a case of a fisherman who died unjustly.
For this issue,
Commander Duan was angry.
He took off his uniform,
He was even imprisoned for more than a year.
Tell me, a policeman like this,
How could he get involved in this?
Are you sure you are talking about Li Cheng Rui?
Yes.
man,
If he wants something, he must bear his burden.
Because of his current position and authority at the police station,
He must submit to higher officials.
So its current appearance
Flatterer and flatterer
Very normal.
This is Feng Huang Police Station
He can't do without you.
I, Jiang Si Yao, even if I'm no longer a policewoman,
I can still investigate cases.
Come back.
Wait.
Police card.
tell me,
How could Peter die by such a coincidence?
Right under her feet?
Maybe it's fate.
Who is responsible for this issue?
The person in charge of this case is Detective Jiang.
if,
She was issued a suspension order for investigation.
This way you can silence people's tongues.
Yes, you are correct, Mr. Mayor.
You can't blame me.
In these difficult times,
The ability to protect oneself
Very difficult indeed.
Has the matter you talked about been arranged?
It's done.
You can go to the police station at any time.
This outfit looks good.
Isn't it? I think so.
Little thief, how did you get here?
You're wearing a police uniform too.
Why are you here too?
I said I would come to help my older sister.
I said I would help Si Yao.
What is your opinion?
I look handsome in a police uniform, don't I?
Where is my older sister?
Sergeant Lee called her into his office.
Si Yao.
Big sister, this is my appointment letter.
This is an appointment.
This is a letter suspending me from work for investigation.
I'll go look for Huo Qishan.
I will go and demand justice for you.
I am waiting.
It is true that I was suspended from work,
But you can do it.
Top priority now
She is to find the missing girl Lingling.
Good.
Foreign clothes.
Revealing.
It promotes immorality and immorality
Aliens music
Her tones are sharp
Take lives
Aliens machines
Cunning tricks
It cuts people's livelihoods
Aliens' cannons and rifles
Invade lands
And slaughter innocents
short
Everything related to foreigners
It aims to occupy the lands of the peoples of the East
So, only under the leadership of the East God
Heavenly Master Gu Mang
We can eliminate everything that is foreign
Reviving our traditions
Eliminate everything foreign
Revive our traditions
Straighten your behavior and guard your heart
Start with yourselves
In the photos taken by Peter
Most girls are in this age group
The disappearance of those girls must have something to do with Peter
Dear colleague
This is my first time working as a policeman
Teach me how to start an investigation
Go check out the surrounding neighborhoods
To see if there are any girls missing
Good
its object
Go to Bai Xiang Building
this...
I?
Lingling disappeared there
You have to pretend to be you
A client is looking for a dancer to spend the night with
Go and check
Isn't this bad?
I had never looked for a dancer before
No no
I wanted to tell you last time
This type of clothing does not suit you
Next suit
This is already the seventh suit
Can't we stop changing?
no
I'm not just meeting a dancer
Why am I wearing clothes?
In this flashy way?
Can't we use a trick?
I have asked someone to inquire specifically
This dancer's name is Liu Yingxiang
She was previously the top star of Changlemen
And now she is the owner of the Bai Xiang Building
She is only interested in young gentlemen
Who have returned from studying abroad
You little thief
You are now our hope
In the entire police department
No one is more suitable than you
This role is yours alone
This is the last suit
If it doesn't fit, there's no other choice
You little thief
This casual suit looks on you
Really special
I'm counting on you